wsiworld.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy - WSI

## WSI’s Privacy Statement

* * *

Last Updated: April 2018

**At WSI, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.  
**This Privacy Statement provides important information on how WSI (““ **we** ,” “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) handles personal information. This Privacy Statement applies to all information gathered for and on behalf of WSI electronically through the wsiworld.com site (the “ **Site** ”). It explains data collection, use and disclosure of personal information by WSI. It does not apply to offline products or services.

By accessing the Site or providing us with any personal information, you agree that WSI may collect, use and disclose such personal information. In addition, it also signifies that you agree with all the terms of this Privacy Statement.

WSI welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you have questions concerning WSI Privacy Statement, please contact us at [policy@wsiworld.com](mailto:policy@wsiworld.com) or via postal mail at the address provided below:

Privacy Officer, WSI  
20 Carlson Court, Suite 100  
Etobicoke, Ontario  
Canada, M9W 7K6

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to determine and address your concerns promptly.

### Who are we?

* * *

WSI holds over two decades of digital marketing experience and is the world’s largest and most innovative digital marketing agency network, with hundreds of offices worldwide.

### Personal Data Collection

* * *

#### What is personal information?

Personal information is any information that identifies you, or by which your identity could reasonably be ascertained or deduced from that information.

#### How do we collect personal information from you?

The collection of personal information is obtained when a visitor lands on the Site, you use the Site through completing a form to gain more information or if you register to receive our monthly newsletters, download resources or request to speak with a customer support representative or a WSI consultant.

#### Why are we collecting your personal information?

WSI collects information in order to provide better and enhanced services to you. The information requested on this Site is required to process your request for more information about our company, services, and products, register for our events or monthly newsletters, contact customer support or a WSI Consultant.

We may also use your personal information to detect and reduce fraud and credit risk for the purchasing of a franchise, service or product.

#### What type of personal information is collected?

The personal information WSI collects may include but is not limited to your name, mailing address, home phone number, cell phone number or financial and credit card information, if required, for the purchase of WSI products or services or registration of  WSI events. Your company or business name, business address, your business contact information or information that is already a matter of public record or knowledge is generally not considered personal information and may be shared with anyone within or outside the WSI network.

#### Why WSI creates a profile

We may analyze your personal information to create a profile of personal information so that we can segment you and contact you with relevant information about our company, services or products. We may make use of additional information about you if, available from external sources to help us do this effectively.

#### How we use your personal information

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to:

  * Navigate through the Site
  * Provide the service(s)
  * Carry out the transaction(s) you have requested

In support of these uses, WSI may use personal information to:

  * Provide you with more effective customer service
  * Provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications
  * Send you information about other WSI products and services

### Transferring Your Information

* * *

As part of the services offered to you through the Site, the information which you provide to WSI may be transferred to a local WSI Consultant outside of Canada to provide you the service. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to Canada.

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. If we transfer your information outside of Canada in this way, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Privacy Statement.

### Personal Information Access & Control

* * *

WSI, will not sell or rent your information to third parties, or share your information with third parties for marketing purposes outside of WSI digital marketing services. Access to your personal information will be restricted to WSI employees, administrators or WSI Consultants who are responsible for the marketing and administration of WSI services.

#### How do I access my personal information?

If you wish to access your personal information, update your details, or unsubscribe from communications, emails us at [policy@wsiworld.com](mailto:policy@wsiworld.com) or write to:

Privacy Officer, WSI  
20 Carlson Court, Suite 100  
Etobicoke, Ontario  
Canada, M9W 7K6

#### How do I control WSI use of my personal information?

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of WSI employees, administrators or WSI Consultants who are responsible for the marketing and administration of WSI services without your permission. As described above in the previous section, you can access your personal information through email or writing to us.

#### Links to other websites and social media

This Site hosts various blogs, case studies, and testimonials that will allow you to share our content through various Social Media Applications with other users. Any personal information that you contribute to any Social Media Application can be read, collected and used by these Social Media Organizations. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other Social Media Applications and their Organization.

In addition, the Site may contain links to other websites managed by other organizations or WSI Consultants; this Privacy Statement only applies to wsiworld.com. If you landed on our Site from a third party website, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices outside of our Site. We encourage you to check the third party sites or social media applications privacy statements.

### Personal Information Protection

* * *

WSI is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities.

### Cookies & Similar Technologies

* * *

This Site uses cookies to deliver relevant content, ease site navigation or collect information for statistical use, such as how many visitors our site received. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies at any time by modifying the settings in your browser, and you can also erase cookies from your operating system as well. However, declining or erasing cookies may preclude you from fully experiencing all the features of this website.

For more information about cookies and how we use them, please read our [Cookies & Internet Advertising Policy](https://www.wsiworld.com/cookie-policy/).

### Consent

* * *

If you have voluntarily provided personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, your name, title, phone number, or email address (business or personal), you have assumed an implied business relationship with WSI and therefore consented to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Statement.

WSI will not use personally identifiable information for any purpose outside of the implied business relationship.

#### Children’s Privacy Protection

WSI is committed to protecting the privacy of children locally and internationally. This Site is not designed or intentionally targeted towards children 16 years of age or younger, and we do not intentionally collect or maintain personal information about anyone under the age of 16.

#### WSI opt-in Approach

WSI will ensure to act in compliance with Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation (CASL) and Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA), and the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). In order to ensure compliance, electronic messages (including email marketing) will be based on an “Opt-In” approach.

WSI will gain consent for external electronic messages purposes prior to sending commercial messages (including emails) unless we have a pre-existing business relationship with the client or prospect as in these particular cases consent is considered to be implied. Should WSI require personal information for a new purpose, we will contact you directly to seek consent for that new use/purpose.

#### How can you opt-out?

Your consent to the use of personal information to communicate with you and offer you franchise opportunities, products and services are optional. If you wish to remove your personal information from our databases, you may opt-out at any time by doing the following: unsubscribing through a delivered email message, contacting us directly via email at [policy@wsiworld.com](mailto:policy@wsiworld.com) to make this request, or write to:

Privacy Officer, WSI  
20 Carlson Court, Suite 100  
Etobicoke, Ontario  
Canada, M9W 7K6

### Review of this Privacy Statement

* * *

This Privacy Statement is in accordance with Canada’s Anti-Spam Law (CASL) effective July 1, 2014 and Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”) effective January 1, 2001, California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA) effective February 6, 2013, and the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) effective May 25, 2018.

We keep this Privacy Statement under regular review. We encourage you to periodically review this document to be informed about how WSI protects and respects your personal information. This Privacy Statement was **last updated in April 2018**.
